# **Barak Cohen**

### Javascript Developer

052-5797294 baaraak0@gmail.com github.com/baaraak linkedin.com/in/barak-cohen92/

#### About me

I'm passionate front end engineer with experience developing complex, high profile web applications collaborating with both small and large teams. I specialise in JavaScript, familiar with the agile environment and leveraging modern technologies such as React and Redux. Familiar with server-side languages like Node.js and PHP.

## **Experience**

### **Amdocs**

Software Engineer - React.js Developer (Nov 2017 - Aug 2019)

- Build complex front end applications from scratch using React.js and redux.
- Experience with UI/UX design, optimize across various screen sizes and cross-browser.
- · Design and implement crucial business features.
- · Writing unit tests.
- · Working in agile methodology.

### Techfinancials - Herzliya

Fullstack Developer - PHP, Wordpress, React.js (May 2016 - Oct 2017)

- Build responsive web and mobile web applications from scratch.
- · Design and develop new business features.
- · Design and develop new business features.
- Create new WordPress themes and plugins for customers.
- · Scrum master, control over agile process in the team.

#### **Skills**

- JavaScript
- Node.js
- HTML5
- CSS3 / SCSS / Styled-components
- Animations

- React
- Redux, Redux-thunk/saga/toolkit
- Webpack, Babel, Gulp
- Enzyme, Jest, Cypress
- CI/CD

- · Responsive Design
- · Mysql, MongdoDB
- · GraphQL, Apollo
- PHP
- Wordpress

### **Education**

## Full-stack web development.

HackerU College (2015 - May 2016)

- Full stack web development at HackerU college.
- PHP, MySQL, Laravel, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, JQuery, SEO.

# Languages

- Hebrew Fluent.
- English Good.